# Naglaa Modawi Mohammed Front-End Developer

naglaamodawi@gmail.com +249929696244

#### **Profile**

Front end developer with 2+ years experience I have designed and developed several front end application as **freelancer** using JavaScript, Bootstrap then I have joined **Sudan University** front End team and I have redesigned and developed some Website Colleges in Sudan University using HTML, CSS, React JS and Bootstrap framework. And worked as **teaching Assistant** in The College of **Computer Science**, Sudan University of Science and Technology teaching the practical side of web application course.

Since the beginning I have been obsessed with new technology. I am **co-founder** of the **Baranda** Company initiative which has virtual tours, i responsible for all **Technical issues** in this company.

# **Work Experience**

## Front end Developer, web designer

Baranda Company February 2021 — Present

- In this company, I am responsible for a number of tasks, the beginnings of determining the structure and design of the website, Re-transform the design into actual code, And finally, upload the website to the server
- optimizing web pages from maximum speed website
- Building reusable code for future use

## **Teaching assistant**

Sudan University Of Science And Technology February 2020 - July 2021

Teaching the practical Side of the web application Course.

## Front end developer

Sudan university of science and information technology October 2019 - October 2020

## Job Description

- Convert the UI/UXdesign into organized and clear code.
- Analyzing previous pages then modifying them and correction errors in them.

## **Education**

Bachelor / Computer System And Networks Sudan University Of Science And Technology October 2014 - November 2018

#### Skills

- Front end Developer tools
- Frameworks and Libraries
- Web Performance Optimization
- Google Analytics
- Git and Github

#### Certifications

## Nafeer for Software - Capacity Building Program

National Information Center 25July - 30/July 2020

## **UX Design**

Edraak platform June /2020

## **Professional Skills**

Zafar Training Center 20/9 - 28/9/2020

# **Project Management**

Edrak Platform May 2020

# **Business Development**

Zafar Training Center 15/11 - 19/11

## Link

Some of my previous projects

- Blueteel.com
- http://baranda4xr.com
- <a href="https://naglaamodawi.github.io/My-Portfolio/">https://naglaamodawi.github.io/My-Portfolio/</a>
- <a href="https://naglaamodawi.github.io/HardTarget\_/">https://naglaamodawi.github.io/HardTarget\_/</a>
- https://naglaamodawi.github.io/Tourism/index.htm